<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://hl7.org/fhir ../../src-generated/schemas/fhir-single.xsd" lang="en">

  <blockquote class="stu-note">
    <p>The specification herewith documented is for the time being a working specification, and may not be used for any implementation purposes. 
    No liability can be inferred from the use or misuse of this specification, or its consequences.</p>
  </blockquote>

  <a name="scope"></a>
  <h3>Scope</h3>
  <p>
    This is the Laboratory Report HL7 FHIR Implementation Guide for the XPanDH project, created to assist the work of the pilots for the <a href="#adoption-domains">XpanDH exprimentation bubbles</a>.
  </p>

  <a name="project"></a>
  <h3>The project</h3>

  <a name="mission"></a>
  <h4>The mission</h4>
  <p>Help individuals and organizations successfully adopt the European Electronic Health Record Exchange Format (EEHRxF) in a way that is empowering and supportive.
  </p>

  <a name="how"></a>
  <h4>How to:</h4>
  <p>Mobilizing and building capacity to ensure the widespread adoption of the European Electronic Health Records Exchange Format (EEHRxF) across Europe. 
  </p>
  <p>More details in <a href="https://xpandh-project.iscte-iul.pt/">XpanDH Web Site</a>

  </p>

  <a name="adoption-domains"></a>
  <h3>XpanDH Adoption Domains/X-Bubbles</h3>
  <a name="mission"></a>

  <a name="what-is-adoption-domain"></a>
  <h4>What is:</h4>
  <p>An EEHRxF adoption domain could be considered as an instantiation of a use case, with a specific case application, that has meaning from a health system or clinical perspective, with defined implementable requirements (simple if only one EEHRxF priority category is uses or composite if data from more than one is required), that satisfies all the conditions for users to be ready to implement data exchange in conformity to EEHRxF guidelines and specifications 
  </p>
  <p>XpanDH will exercise a set of adoption domains, involving Hospitals, Regional/National organziation, vendors,.., thorugh experimentaion bubbles (in the Hpandh jargon called X-Bubbles)</p>

  <a name="covered-adoption-domain"></a>
  <h4>Adoption domains / X-Bubbles covered by this guide:</h4>
  <ul>
    <li>X-Bubble 1: OKFO; organisation to organisation (national level). Communicate a specific set of laboratory results of patients between different organisations so that each organisation can maintain a complete record of the results, in order to ensure continuity of care, and possibility to generate alerts to their General Practitioner (GP), nurse, etc.</li>
    <li>X-Bubble 2: CHUP; organisation to patient (national level). Communicate the latest set of laboratory results to the patient so they can follow up on any pre-agreed actions, track their progress and contact the treating clinician with any concerns or questions.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>More details on X-Bubbles and Adoption Doamin in XpanDH deliverable D1.4 and D4.1<a href="https://xpandh-project.iscte-iul.pt/">XpanDH Web Site</a>
  </p>

  <a name="dependencies"></a>
  <h3>Dependencies</h3>

{% include dependency-table.xhtml %}

  <a name="x-versions"></a>
  <h3>Cross Version Analysis</h3>

{% include cross-version-analysis.xhtml %}

  <a name="global"></a>
  <h3>Global Profiles</h3>

{% include globals-table.xhtml %}

  <a name="authors"></a>
  <h3>Authors and Contributors</h3>


</div>